{
    "frontend": [
        {
            
            "question": "What is html",
            "answer": "hypertext markup language"
        },
        {
            
            "question": "What is CSS",
            "answer": "Cascading style sheet"
        },
        {
            
            "question": "which language is used to add interactivity to webpages",
            "answer": "Javascript"
        },

        {
           "question": "Which HTML tag is used to create a hyperlink?",
           "answer": "<a> tag"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which HTML tag is used to create an ordered list in a webpage?",
            "answer": "<ol> tag"
        }
    ],

    "backend": [
        {
            
            "question": "What is API",
            "answer": "Application Programming interface"
        },
        {
            
            "question": "Which language is mostly used for backend",
            "answer": "Java, php"
        },
        {
            
            "question": "what does this HTTP 404 status code means",
            "answer": "Page not found"
        },
        {
            "question": "How to initialize Git repository",
            "answer": "using git init"
        },
        {
            "question": "How to switch branches on Git",
            "answer": "git switch branchname"
        }
    ]
}